SHAILESH MAKWANA

Digital Sales Deputy Manager

To whomsoever it may concern

Dear Sir/Madam,

I would very much like to discuss opportunities with your organization. Please see from my enclosed resume and if that meets your requirements.

To schedule an interview, please reach out to me by any medium provided in my contact info.

Thank you for taking time to review my application, I look forward to talking with you.

Sincerely, Shailesh Makwana

Last Update Date: 5th March, 2023

PROFILE

Analyze data to identify sales opportunities. Develop promotional ideas and material. Continually track digital media metrics and KPIs to ensure growth. Conduct continuous research on the latest industry trends and consumer behavior analysis to develop innovative ideas for the market to generate further revenue.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 88661 02552





EMAIL:

makwana.shailesh786@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Master of Arts

Ahmedabad, April 2006 Gujarat University Percentage: 50%

Bachelor of Arts

Ahmedabad, April 2004 Gujarat University Percentage: 45%

12th General Stream

Ahmedabad, April 2001 Gujarat Higher Secondary Education Board

Percentage: 64%

10th General Stream

Ahmedabad, April 1999 Gujarat Secondary Education Board Percentage: 50%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Angel One Broking Ltd - Digital Sales Deputy Manager

Ahmedabad – June 2021 till the time

- Handling Team With 20 CSR each
- Online Sales Plan Day/week/Month wise Planning
- Sales Team Headlining & coaching Associate
- Sales Training and improve Associates Skill
- Cross sale (Mutual Fund/Term Plan/insurance)
- Ensuring 100% Achievement of Team Member's KRA.
- Managing In-house Escalation and Ensuring its resolution from client's end
- Maintain performance and Quality.
- Client coordination and update as per Criteria
- Every month Team outing, and team meet
- Actively participating in all Happy world activities
- Maintain Manpower and Planning Roistering
- Performance Review with center Manager
- Sales & Convince

5paisa Capital IIFL - Digital Sales Team Leader

Ahmedabad - January 2018 to May 2021

- Handling Team With 25 CSR
- Online Sales Plan Day/week/Month wise Planning
- Sales Team Headlining & coaching Associate
- Sales Training and improve Associates Skill
- Cross sale (Mutual Fund/Term Plan/Advisory Services/gold Loan and collection)
- Ensuring 100% Achievement of Team Member's KRA.
- Brokerage Plan cross Sales
- Maintain MIS and Quality
- Observation Calls and Feedback same time
- Coaching and Training
- Live monitor floor meaning
- Performance review Weekly/Monthly
- Hiring new employees and onboarding
- Generate Revenue in sales
- Employee Qualifier incentives
- Excel formulas /PowerPoint presentation/ Email Education

Aegis BPO – Team Leader

Ahmedabad – February 2009 to August 2017

- Handling Team With 35 CSR
- Plan Roster Daily/Weekly/Monthly
- Live Audit and Monitor Calls
- Client coordination and update SL/AL as per Criteria
- Maintain performance and Quality
- Ensuring 100% Achievement of Team Member's KRA.
- Managing In-house Escalation and Ensuring its resolution from client's
- Maintain AHT/Shrinkage/ Quality/Attrition/
- Hiring new employees and onboarding
- Appreciate Employee for excellent work
- Coaching and Training
- Customer Service
- Convincing power
- Build better customer relationships
- Cross Sales Data Plan/Caller tune Plan/Reactivate existing client

Last Update Date: 5th March, 2023

Hutch CSR BPO Call Center

Ahmedabad – March 2007 to February 2009

- Working As a CSR
- Daily take a Briefing
- Active Listing to new Plans
- Understood product and planning
- Client Complaint / Request / Query Handling
- Calls Handling and Provide customer service
- Handling HNI Clients
- Guide to Properly Product and Plan with Client
- Daily Report send Manager
- Achieving Rewards Top Gun
- Deliver delightful customer experience

EXTRA TECHNICAL CERTIFICATIONS

Diploma in Multilingual Office Automation & Financial Accounting

From C-DAC, 2005-06 with Grade A

Hardware & Networking IT

From CHNA, 2013-15 with Grade A

Spoken English

From Bright, 2008 with Grade A

OTHER ACHIEVEMENTS

Shortcut To INDRA (Customer Report Live Check) in Aegis

From Award for Tata Found Shortcut Key Data, 2010

Monthly R&R

From Aegis, 2011

Monthly Lowest Attrition

From Aegis, 2013

Monthly Lowest AHT

From Aegis, 2014

Highest Activation (R&R PAN India)

From 5 Paisa Capital IIFL, 2018

120% Target Achievement (Quarterly)

From Angel One, 2021

SKILLS

